audiogon.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy – Audiogon

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to audiogon.com and Audiogon, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Audiogon, Inc. including audiogon.com and Audiogon. The Audiogon website is an eCommerce site. By using the Audiogon website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Audiogon may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:

  * First and Last Name

  * Mailing Address

  * E-Mail Address

  * Phone Number

If you purchase Audiogon’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Audiogon’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. 

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Use of your Personal Information

Audiogon collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. 

Audiogon may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Audiogon and its affiliates.

Sharing Information with Third Parties

Audiogon does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Audiogon may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Audiogon may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Audiogon, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Audiogon may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Audiogon or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Audiogon; and/or (c) act under the exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Audiogon, or the public.

Tracking User Behavior

Audiogon may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Audiogon, in order to determine what Audiogon services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Audiogon to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Automatically Collected Information

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Audiogon. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Audiogon website.

We use Stripe as a payment service. Stripe collects identifying information about the devices that connect to its services. Stripe uses this information to operate and improve the services it provides to us, including for fraud detection. You can learn more about Stripe and read its privacy policy at [https://stripe.com/privacy](https://stripe.com/privacy).

Use of Cookies

The Audiogon website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Audiogon pages, or register with Audiogon site or services, a cookie helps Audiogon to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Audiogon website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Audiogon features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept of decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Audiogon services or websites you visit.

How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals  
Some internet browsers have incorporated "Do Not Track" features. Most of these features, when turned on, send a signal or preference (the "DNT Signal") to the web sites you visit indicating that you do not wish to be tracked. Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret DNT Signals, nor a common definition of "tracking", we do not currently respond to DNT Signals on the Audiogon Websites. Audiogon engages in so-called online behavioral advertising on third-party sites (also sometimes called "retargeting" or “tracking”), through which information collected about the pages you visit on Audiogon is used to display ads for Audiogon products or services on third-party websites. This information may uniquely identify a browser but is not personally identifiable.

Online Behavioral Advertising  
Audiogon may use third-party online advertising companies to provide you with Audiogon advertisements that may be relevant to your interests, as determined by your activity on Audiogon and non-Audiogon websites. This type of ad customization is known as "online behavioral” or “interest-based” advertising. These advertising companies may use cookies to understand your interests based on, for example, pages visited and browsing patterns on Audiogon and non-Audiogon websites.

Opting Out of Online Behavioral Advertising  
You may opt-out of receiving online behavioral advertisements from third-party advertising companies that Audiogon uses to serve these interest-based ads. Because Audiogon participates in the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) self-regulatory program, we have adopted the use of the DAA’s Advertising Options Icon (AdChoices) on these ads for the purpose of allowing users the ability to opt-out of this form of tracking. You may click on the AdChoices icon to opt out of receiving behaviorally-targeted ads that are served to you based on your browsing behavior on Audiogon websites. Please note that opting out through the AdChoices icon will only affect ads served to you based on your behavior on Audiogon websites, and does not prevent you from receiving other Audiogon advertising. You may also opt out of receiving behaviorally-targeted ads directly at our website using this link:  [AdChoices](http://www.schwab.com/public/schwab/nn/legal_compliance/privacy/online_privacy/adchoice_redirect.html). Opting out through the Audiogon website, as opposed to using the AdChoices icon, means the data about your behaviors on Audiogon websites won’t be used by third party advertising companies to serve you interest-based ads. 

The methods of both collecting data for the purpose of serving behaviorally-targeted ads and recording your opt-out are done at the individual computer browser level and are based on browser cookies. If you clear your cookies or use a different browser or computer, you will need to re-submit your preference to the specified third-party advertising companies. For more information about behavioral advertising, please visit http://www.aboutads.info.

Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. 

Security of your Personal Information

Audiogon secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Audiogon uses the following methods for this purpose:

  * SSL Protocol

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

 We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

Children Under Thirteen

Audiogon does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent of guardian for permission to use this website.

Disconnecting your Audiogon Account from Third-Party Websites

You will be able to connect your Audiogon account to third-party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR AUDIOGON ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD-PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO TH E CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD-PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED IN THIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third-party account at any time. Users may disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting their Account Settings on those third-party sites and revoking access to Audiogon.

E-mail Communication

From time to time, Audiogon may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from Audiogon or click on a link therein.

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Audiogon, you may opt out of such communications by clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE button at the bottom of all email communications, or managing your notification preferences in your Account Settings.

External Data Storage Sites

We may store your data on servers provided by third-party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.

Changes to this Statement

Audiogon reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.

Contact Information

Audiogon welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Audiogon has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Audiogon at:

Audiogon, LLC

105 East North Street

Suite 102

Greenville, SC 29601

Email Address:

Effective as of March 21, 2018
